

Contact me

O Kottayam, India

safalalikhan@gmail.com

safalalikhan

in safalalikhan

safalalikhan.com

+91-8137888877

Education

Attended BTech in Information Technology,

Cochin University of Science
And Technology,
2014-08 - 2018-05

Back-End Web Development,

★ Masai School, 2022-01 - 2022-09

Technical Skills

Java | SQL | Git | Spring | DSA

Soft Skills

Creativity | Problem-solving | Adaptability | Leadership | Time management

Interests

Travel | Football | Cycling

Accomplishments

- Volunteered in Mozilla Maker Party (Kochi)
- Mathematics Club Secretary (School Level)
- College Football Champion (University Level)

Safal Ali Khan

Back-End Developer

Professional Profile

Creative and diligent back-end developer with experience in more than 10 projects. Eager to work and constantly improve skills. Creative and always ready to solve any problems coming his way. Have experience running own startup and business for more than 4 years, managing different teams.

Work Experience

Organization: Travethon

Position: Co-Founder

Duration: 2018-06 to 2020-03

ROLES:

Travel Planner | Poster Designing

Organization: Zameer Garments

Position: Manager

Duration: 2020-03 to 2022-01

ROLES:

Sales | Purchase Manager | Operations

Projects

Bobbi Brown Clone

Premium Cosmetics Brand Online Website

Features

- Dropdown Menus and Sliders
- Signup and Login functionalities

Tech-Stack

JavaScript | CSS | HTML | Git

Area of responsibility

Full Stack Developer

Web Application (7)

Basic Application built completely on Java.

Features

- Efficient
- · Interactive

Tech-Stack

Java | SQL | Git | Spring | Spring Boot

Area of responsibility

· Back-End Developer